## CURRICULUM VITAE FOR JONATH.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Nabasa Jonath

Sex: Female

Nationality: Ugandan

Marital Status: Single

Date of Birth: 1<sup>st</sup> January 1987

Contact- Telephone number: 0702103145/0784871487.

Email Address: <a href="mailto:nabasajonahdesire@gmail.com">nabasajonahdesire@gmail.com</a>

### **CAREER OBJECTIVE:**

Desire to work in a highly competitive and dynamic organization and project with commitment to attaining goals, sense of delivery of excellent services to the organization and its esteemed clients where self-motivation, creativity and dedication as an individual and as part of the team is highly valued.

## **KEY QUALIFICATIONS**

Jonath has 5 years' experience in conducting Environmental Assessments for development projects. She has carried out Environmental Impact Assessments and Environmental Audits. As a research associate/trainee in reputable environmental consultancy firms, Jonath participates in conducting various Environmental and Social Impact Assessments (ESIA) and Environmental Audits (EA); and preparing Environmental and Social Management Plans (ESMP) for development projects. With a Bachelor's degree in Environmental

science, she is competent enough to tackle environment related concerns and provide rational advice.

## PERSONAL SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Good communication and listening skills
- Creative and Innovative When It Comes to Improving Operations
- Quick learner when understanding functionalities/menus in IT application or systems
- Can work independently and as part of a team to achieve business set goals
- Uphold a Professional work ethic at all times.
- Have good management abilities for teams of 5 to 100 people
- Good command of the English language with excellent writing and reading ability
- Work under minimum supervision
- Good Time Management
- Forward Thinking under Pressure while also handling different tasks at the same time

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

YEAR	INSTITUTION	QUALIFICATION
2007-2010	Makerere	Bachelor's Degree in
	University	Environmental science.
October	Mind power Africa	Certificate in project planning and
2009		management
2005-2006	Valley College	Uganda Advanced Certificate of
	Bushenyi	Education
2001-2004	Rweibaare	Uganda Certificate of Education

	Secondary School	
1993-2000	Rwentuha primary	Primary Leaving Examination
	school	

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**January 2018 to date** Research associate with sustcon consult limited/EIA trainee

**2015 – January 2018:** Research Associate/EIA trainee (Contract), Pinnacle Enviro Consult

**Brief Description**: As a research Associate, I was responsible for undertaking field studies to collect information for Environmental Impact Assessment and Environmental Audit, preparing Environmental Impact Statements and Environmental Audit reports for submission to NEMA. I liaise with relevant stakeholders during the studies to obtain their views regarding the operations of a given project. Also following up with Nema to ensure the EIA/Audit process is finalized.

## Projects undertaken so far;

# Environmental and Social Impact Assessment for:

- Eaton Towers Base Transceiver Stations in Uganda.(country wide) (over 30 sites)
- Kongasis fuel station located along tororo-mbale road in bukhumeka ii village, bumbobi parish, bumbobi sub county in mbale district.

- Fuel station located along musita-mayuge-namayingo-luminobusia-majanji road at gilgil-busu lc1, maina parish, mpungwe Sub County in mayuge district.
- fuel filling station located along tororo-jinja road in malawa village, papoli parish, magola sub county in tororo district
- Service Stations for VIVO Energy Uganda countrywide.
- Graphic Systems warehouses in Namanve Industrial Park.
- Pozzolana mining by Industrial Minerals Ltd in Kasese.
- Warehouse establishment for National Medical Stores in Kajjansi, Wakiso District.
- The China Civil Engineering Construction Corporation (CCECC) proposed quarry, campsite and Asphalt plant sites in Bukedea district by Pinnacle Enviro Consults (August 2015)

# Environmental project briefs

- Environmental project brief for the office block located, on plot 28 hannington road kampala central division, kampala district.
- Hotel built on plot no. 543 block 245, kabalagala, off muyenga road, makindye division in kampala district.
- Environmental project brief for the commercial building located, on plot 99, block 6, katwe central zone katwe ii parish makindye division, kampala district.
- Environmental project brief for the commercial building located at plot 2 & 4, semawata road-ntinda, nakawa division, kampala district

- Environmental Audits for:
  - Nyamwamba Small Hydro power Project in Kasese
  - Mpanga small hydro power plant in kamwenge
  - Bidco factory in jinja.
  - GAPCO Service Stations Countrywide
  - Service Stations for VIVO Energy Uganda
  - Eaton Towers Base Transceiver Stations in Central, Eastern and Western Uganda
  - Oilibya Uganda Service Stations Countrywide

### REFEREES

1. Dr John. Baligira

Lecturer

Faculty of Arts, Makerere University

P.o.Box 7062, Kampala Uganda.

Mobile Number- 0772433162

2. Mr. Arinaitwe Johnson

Director

Sustcon consult limited

P.o.Box 28761, Kampala Uganda.

Mobile Number- 0757202866

3 Mr. William Mukaira

Director

Valley University and Valley College.

Mobile Number - 0772363702